The camera never lies...
Exhibit A is a thriller, drama, horror film directed by Dom Rotheroe.
Exhibit A tells the timely story of a normal family
disintegrating under financial pressure.
All is not as it seems as the King family go about their
day-to-day lives oblivious of the horror to come.
Dad Andy (Bradley Cole) is nursing a secret that ultimately
leads to terrible consequences for them all.
We witness these chilling events unfold through daughter Judith's
video camera, which subsequently becomes Exhibit A.
Andy King, played by Bradley Cole.
Joe King, played by Oliver Lee.
Judith King, played by Brittany Ashworth.
Sheila King, played by Angela Forrest.
Wayne, played by Jason Allen.
Exhibit A is a 2007 British independent psychological thriller film directed
by Dom Rotheroe and produced by Darren Bender for Warp Films.
The film is an example of the found footage genre and stars Bradley
Cole, Brittany Ashworth, Angela Forrest and Oliver Lee.
It was filmed on location in Yorkshire and Suffolk and released
on 1 October 2007 at the Raindance Film Festival.
It was the last film that prolific stuntman Roy Alon worked on.
The film explores themes of espionage, family, found
footage, pseudo-documentary, faux documentary.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.